Hi, I made to translate the picture book system.
This is described in picture book which I made with the service.
There is no knowledge of disaster prevention.
Children can not read the characters.
There are people who would be affected for that.
By using learn to read and write as a child,
Wearing it the knowledge of disaster prevention is important.
"ehon" is children learn to read and write in a picture book,
Platform to acquire knowledge of disaster prevention.
Have provide the right to use
the picture book authors
around the world.
Ask the person who Can you translate, have translated into various languages​​.
I will print picture books that have been translated at school or local communities.
And I will be distributed to children.
Knowledge of disaster prevention that remember picture book, children will talk to people in the family and community.
In this way, "ehon" will spread to people around the world the knowledge of disaster prevention.
The procured and advertising funds needed to maintain the service.
Translator cooperation authors and, platform advocates of picture book come together, and raise children to prevent disaster.
We reduce the disaster from the world in the picture book.
Please see a demo of the site.
Upload the image of the picture book.
Select the area of character.
I will determine the position of the character easily be traced.
I choose the language and title.
I will continue to enter one after the other translations to a specific area.
Input has ended.
You can translate on the basis of the text already entered.
You can translate it even if you do not understand the language of the original.
You will do the download.
Generate a pdf file that is easy to use.
Person to distribute people to register, people translate, print, do the separate.
Through the use of the printer in the room, it can be completed easily.
You can learn disaster prevention more fun and easy